

MUHAMMAD FAJRUL KHAQ

Web Developer

I am a 7th semester Informatics student at STMIK El Rahma Yogyakarta and have won an award as the best project when participating in SIB Dicoding Batch 3. Apart from that, I also have experience attending a fullstack developer bootcamp at Skilvul.

SKILLS

- FIGMA
- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- BOOTSTRAP
- REACT JS
- NODE JS
- GIT
- EXPRESS JS
- MY SQL
- MONGO DB

EDUCATION

Information Engineering

Institution: Stmik El Rahma Yogyakarta 2020 - Now

• Current GPA: 3.77

EXPERIENCE

Pengembang Front-End Web dan Back-End

August 2022 to December 2022 (4 months)

I am participating in the Certified Independent Study (SIB) by Dicoding, Batch 3, and I have chosen the Front-End Web and Back-End Developer packages. In this program, I am learning the JavaScript programming language.

FullStack Web Developer

August 2023 to December 2023 (4 months)

I am received a scholarship for the Job-Ready Coding Bootcamp, which is a collaboration between YCAB and Skilvul. In this program, I am learning full-stack web development with the JavaScript programming language.

CONTACT



+6288226946694



Fajrulm05@gmail.com



in Muhammad Fajrul Khaq



Fajrull



https://fajrulv2.netlify.app/

ACHIEVEMENT

- · Selected as the best capstone project in the SIB Dicoding X Kampus Merdeka Batch 3 program with the title 'Growth Familie'.
- Recipient of the 2023 Youth Digital Acceleration Scholarship.

CERTIFICATES

Belajar Dasar Git dengan GitHub

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 10P86MJELXQK

Aug 13, 2022

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: <u>JMZVGL7NRZN9</u>

Aug 3, 2022

Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk

Pemula

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 10P86KYW2XQK

Sep 5, 2022

Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web

Development

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 6RPNDLYLRZ2M

Sep 18, 2022

Menjadi Front-End Web Developer Expert

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 07Z6GG1RRXQR

Nov 8, 2022

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: EYX497WV6PDL

Oct 25, 2022

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End

untuk Pemula

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 81P283NNJPOY

Nov 12, 2022

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Web dengan

React

Dicoding Indonesia

CredentialsID: 6RPN46EJQX2M

Sep 17, 2023